<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="app_name">SQRL Login</string>
<string name="introduction_startpage"><b>Biztonságos Gyors Megbízható Bejelentkezés</b>\n\nÜdvözlünk a súgó oldalain, melyek részletesen elmagyarázzák a protokoll elemeit. Megpróbáljuk felvázolni a különböző eseteket az alkalmazás használatához.\n\nA súgóban jobbra/balra húzással tudsz az oldalak között navigálni.\n\nHa érdekel az alkalmazás forráskódja, ezen a címen érheted el: <a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a></string>
<string name="introduction_nutshell"><b>Dióhéjban</b>\n\nMielőtt bejelentkezéshez használhatnád az SQRL-t, létre kell hoznod a privát azonosítódat. Ebből csak egyre van szükséged, talán egész életedben, mivel SEMMIT nem fed fel rólad és különösen biztonságos. Valójában egy nagyon hosszú (77 számjegyű) véletlenszám.\n\nEzután, ha SQRL-lel jelentkezel be egy weboldalra, a privát azonosítód segítségével generálunk egy újabb 77 jegyű véltelenszámot a weboldal számára. Minden weboldal amit meglátogatsz különböző számként lát, és minden alkalommal mikor visszatérsz ugyanarra az oldalra az oldal száma újragenerálódik.\n\nEzáltal egyedileg és véglegesen azonosítható vagy, mégis teljesen névtelen.\n\nMivel nincs szükség e-mail cím vagy jelszó használatára, soha nem adod ki a valódi identitásodat, így a weboldalnak nem is kell megőriznie azt. Ha a weboldalon tárolt SQRL azonosítókat el is lopják, ezek az azonosítók csak ezen az egy helyen használhatók fel, ráadásul az SQRL-be épített titkosítás lehetetlenné teszi az ellopott azonosítók használatát.\n\nPontosan olyan jó, amilyennek hangzik. Ez az, amire vártunk.</string>
<string name="introduction_password"><b>Az SQRL jelszavad</b>\n\nAz SQRL felszabadít bejelentkezés súlya alól azzal, hogy megcsinálja helyetted. De ez azt is jelenti, hogy ha valaki megszerzi az SQRL alkalmazásodat, meg tud személyesíteni téged.\n\nEzt egy SQRL jelszó használatával küszöböljük ki, melyet TE használsz hogy bejelentkezz az SQRL-be. Te döntöd el, milyen erős védelemre van szükséged. Te választod ki a saját jelszavadat, annak hosszát és komplexitását. A találgatás megelőzése érdekében beállíthatod mennyi ideig tartson a jelszavad feldolgozása. És a hosszabb és bonyolultabb jelszavak használatád megkönnyítendő a jelszó első négy karakterének újbóli begépelése elegendő a jelszó felfrissítéséhez.\n\nJelszavadat és annak beállításait bármikor szabadon megváltoztathatod. És ha bármikor elfelejtenéd vagy elveszítenéd, az SQRL mentő kódját tudod használni hogy újra hozzáférj az azonosítódhoz.</string>
<string name="introduction_rescue_code"><b>SQRL\'s Rescue Code</b>\n\nYou and SQRL will probably never need rescuing. But SQRL\'s security is so tight that you MIGHT need a way to unlock things a bit. Here are the two scenarios where you WOULD need rescuing:\n\n• If you changed your password and the new one slipped your mind, there\'s no one to ask. Unlike websites, where you click I forgot my password, your SQRL app doesn\'t know it either. If it did, it could be hacked and used to steal your identity. Backups you have made of your identity will have been saved under the password you were using then, so that might help. But your SQRL-assigned Rescue Code will always forgive any memory lapse.\n• Once you have established your SQRL identity with a website, that identity can ONLY be changed with ITS Rescue Code. If someone WERE to somehow steal your SQRL identity (if your phone was stolen and you used a VERY weak or guessable password, or malware infected your device), they could never replace your identity with theirs. But YOU could retake your stolen identity by creating a new one and using the old identity\'s Rescue Code (which the bad guys would never have) to replace that old identity with your new one.\n\nSQRL\'s Rescue Code is a powerful ally. Write it down, keep it safe and never lose it. You will probably never need it, but if you do you\'ll be very glad you kept it.</string>
<string name="introduction_backup"><b>Why Backup?</b>\n\nYour SQRL private identity is a randomly chosen 77-digit number used to generate each of your individual web identities. NO ONE knows what it is. As you use SQRL to identify yourself to the Internet, your identity BECOMES that 77-digit number. If it is ever lost, so is your Internet identity.\n\nThe other reason to backup your private identity is to copy it to another computer or mobile device. Once your one private SQRL identity has been installed into all of your devices, you can use any of them to easily identify yourself on the Internet.\n\nSQRL provides many simple ways to back up your private identity, and all backups are ALWAYS protected by your SQRL password and Rescue Code.\n\nPrinting backups onto paper, as a small QR code and text (perhaps more than once) is recommended since paper is the original data storage medium. In many ways, it\'s still the best. Simply store it where you store your life\'s other important documents. You can also record your backup to thumb drives, burn them to CD\'s, and store them safely anywhere.\n\nBut PLEASE do make backups, since NO ONE knows your unique 77-digit private identity… not even you!</string>
<string name="welcome_message"><b>Welcome to the Secure Quick Reliable Login (SQRL) client.</b>\n\nThis client app will help you securely and effortlessly log in to websites supporting the SQRL protocol. \n\nIt safely stores and lets you manage your SQRL identity, which the app uses to create unique per-site logins, which are anonymous and give the website owner no secrets to keep.\n\nThere is no connection to any personal information. It just verifies that the same phone that authenticated last time is the same even this time. This makes it possible to create a unique anonymous login on your favorite sites, and you decide how much data you share with the site.\n\nJust to be clear, this application will not hide any identifiers that your phone may provide, but it will not provide any extra data.\n\nYou start the process by creating an identity or scanning an identity generated by another compatible client (like the desktop client supplied by <a href="https://grc.com">https://grc.com</a>) and open it with your password. When your key is loaded you\'re then able to authenticate by scanning QR codes supplied by websites, verifying the address and choosing to log in.\n\nPlease note that permission to use the camera needs to be supplied in order to scan exported secrets, create identities or scan site QR Codes.\n\nTo follow this project on GitHub you can visit\n<a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a></string>
<string name="button_scan_secret">Azonosító QR kód beolvasása</string>
<string name="button_login">Bejelentkezés</string>
<string name="button_intro_close">Bezárás</string>
<string name="action_help">Súgó</string>
<string name="action_about">Névjegy</string>
<string name="about_message_title">Névjegy</string>
<string name="about_message_text"><b>Secure Quick Reliable Login</b>\n\nVersion: %s\n\nGithub repository:\n<a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a>\n\nAuthors:\nDaniel Persson</string>
<string name="decrypt_identity_message">You\'ve successfully scanned your secure identity. Please verify that the rescue data presented below corresponds to the data printed on your key page.</string>
<string name="communication_incorrect_response">Hibás válasz; a szerver nem hibakóddal válaszolt. Próbáld újra később</string>
<string name="communication_bad_id_association">Bad ID Association: SQRL identity which may be associated with the query nut does not match the SQRL ID used to submit the query.</string>
<string name="communication_client_failure">Kliens hiba: a kérés bizonyos elemeit a szerver nem fogadta el és nem dolgozta fel.</string>
<string name="communication_command_failed">Command failed: The web server has encountered a problem successfully processing the query. </string>
<string name="communication_function_not_supported">Function(s) not supported: Requested one or more SQRL functions, that the server does not currently support.</string>
<string name="communication_sqrl_disabled">SQRL authentication for this identity has previously been locked. To use this identity it needs to be unlocked using rescue code.</string>
<string name="communication_transient_error">Transient error: The server indicates that the signature(s) are correct, but something about the query prevented the command from completing.</string>
<string name="title_activity_main">SQRL - Main</string>
<string name="button_import_identity">Importálás</string>
<string name="button_settings">Beállítások</string>
<string name="button_create_identity">Létrehozás</string>
<string name="button_remove_identity">Eltávolítás</string>
<string name="button_rename_identity">Átnevezés</string>
<string name="button_export_identity">Exportálás</string>
<string name="button_reset_password">Jelszó visszaállítása</string>
<string name="button_rekey_identity">Rekey</string>
<string name="button_change_password">Jelszóváltoztatás</string>
<string name="identity_rename_title">Azonosító átnevezése</string>
<string name="title_activity_show_identity">SQRL - Show identity</string>
<string name="button_rename_ok">Átnevezés</string>
<string name="current_identity_title">Jelenlegi azonosító</string>
<string name="title_activity_clear_identity">SQRL - Clear QuickPass</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked_desc">To be secure, QuickPass should be removed after use.\nClick here to clear it from memory.</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked">Gyors Jelszó aktív</string>
<string name="clear_identity_fail">A Gyors Jelszó még a memóriában van, nem eltávolítható</string>
<string name="clear_identity_success">Gyors Jelszó eltávolítva</string>
<string name="decrypt_identity_fail">Az azonosító visszafejtése nem sikerült, próbáld meg más jelszóval!</string>
<string name="encrypt_identity_fail">Encryption of your newly imported identity failed, please try again</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked_title">Your identity is unlocked in your device memory.</string>
<string name="login_verify_domain_text">Using this protocol you may log in to the scanned URL. Please check that the scanned domain is the same as the place you want to visit before entering password.</string>
<string name="login_domain_title">Do you want to login to:</string>
<string name="change_password_retype">Re-type password</string>
<string name="change_password_current">Jelenlegi jelszó</string>
<string name="change_password_new_password">Kérlek válassz egy új jelszót</string>
<string name="change_password_retyped_password_do_not_match">Retyped password doesn\'t match new password.</string>
<string name="title_activity_settings">SQRL: Beállítások</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length">Gyors Jelszó hossza (karakterekben)</string>
<string name="settings_password_verify">Password verify (seconds)</string>
<string name="settings_idle_timeout">Idle timeout (minutes)</string>
<string name="settings_sqrl_only">Request SQRL only login</string>
<string name="settings_no_sqrl_bypass">Request no SQRL bypass</string>
<string name="settings_save">Mentés</string>
<string name="settings_cancel">Mégsem</string>
<string name="settings_fragment_save">Mentés</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length_not_number">QuickPass input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_idle_timeout_not_number">Idle timeout input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_password_verify_not_number">Password verify input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length_to_large">QuickPass value is too large. (0–255)</string>
<string name="save_settings_password">Jelszó</string>
<string name="save_identity_to">Save identity to</string>
<string name="title_activity_advanced">SQRL: Haladó műveletek</string>
<string name="main_selected_identity">Kiválasztott azonosító</string>
<string name="identity_reset_password">Jelszó visszaállítása</string>
<string name="button_reset_password_ok">Visszaállítás</string>
<string name="reset_password_new">Új jelszó</string>
<string name="reset_password_desc">In order to set a new password without knowing the old one you need to supply the rescue code given to you at identity creation. Then you supply a new password and we will create a password secured identity.</string>
<string name="save_settings_title">Beálítások mentése</string>
<string name="login_title">Bejelentkezés</string>
<string name="import_title">Azonosító importálása</string>
<string name="rename_identity_desc">Új név</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_1">Első rész</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_2">Második rész</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_3">Harmadik rész</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_4">Negyedik rész</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_5">Ötödik rész</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_6">Hatodik rész</string>
<string name="change_password_title">Jelszóváltoztatás</string>
<string name="rescue_code_incorrect_input">A mentő kód részlet négy számjegyből áll</string>
<string name="progress_title">Working</string>
<string name="login_identity_password">Jelszó</string>
<string name="main_identity_removed">Azonosító eltávolítva</string>
<string name="button_lock_account">Fiók zárolása</string>
<string name="button_unlock_account">Fiók zárolás feloldása</string>
<string name="button_remove_account">Fiók eltávolítása</string>
<string name="login_optional_options">További lehetőségek</string>
<string name="button_login_options">Options</string>
<string name="disable_account_title">Fiók zárolása</string>
<string name="button_disable_account">Zárolás</string>
<string name="enable_account_title">Fiók zárolás feloldása</string>
<string name="button_enable_account_enable">Feloldás</string>
<string name="remove_account_title">Fiók eltávolítása</string>
<string name="button_remove_account_remove">Eltávolítás</string>
<string name="button_export_show_identity">Azonosító megjelenítése</string>
<string name="button_export_save_identity">Azonosító mentése</string>
<string name="button_print_identity">Azonosító nyomtatása</string>
<string name="title_activity_url_login">SQRL: Bejelentkezés</string>
<string name="change_password_close">Jelszóváltoztatás ablak bezárása</string>
<string name="export_options_close">Close export options window</string>
<string name="login_close">Bejelentkező ablak bezárása</string>
<string name="login_optional_close">Close login options window</string>
<string name="remove_account_close">Close remove account window</string>
<string name="rename_close">Close rename window</string>
<string name="reset_password_close">Close reset password window</string>
<string name="save_settings_close">Close save settings window</string>
<string name="title_entropy_gather">SQRL: Entrópia gyűjtés</string>
<string name="button_entropy_gather_next">Következő</string>
<string name="scan_site_code">Scan QRCode for site</string>
<string name="scan_identity">Scan QRCode for identity</string>
<string name="title_rescuecode_show">SQRL - Rescue code show</string>
<string name="title_rescuecode_enter">SQRL - Rescue code enter</string>
<string name="button_rekey_identity_start">Indítás</string>
<string name="button_create_identity_start">Indítás</string>
<string name="create_identity_message">Az új azonosító létrehozása hat lépésben történik.\n\n1. Először bekapcsoljuk a kamerát, amit ide-oda mozgatva entrópiát hozol létre a biztonságosabb kulcskészítés érdekében.\n\n2. Ezután megjelenik a mentő kód, amit le kell jegyezned és biztonságban tartanod.\n\n3. Be kell írnod a mentő kódot hogy megbizonyosodjunk róla, hogy valóban lejegyezted.\n\n4. Megadsz egy jelszót az azonosítóhoz.\n\n5. Az alkalmazás elkészíti és titkosítja az azonosítót.\n\n6. Lehetőséged lesz elmenteni ezt az azonosítót egy biztonságos helyre.</string>
<string name="rekey_identity_message">Rekeying your identity is a process done in 7 steps.\n\n1. First, you need to enter the old rescue code for this identity in order to verify that you have access to this security code.\n\n2. Second, the camera will be activated and you wave it around to create entropy to make a more secure key.\n\n3. Next up you will be presented with a new rescue code that you need to record and keep safe.\n\n4. You will be asked to reenter the rescue code in order to verify that it\'s been recorded correctly.\n\n5. You\'ll select a password for your new identity.\n\n6. The application creates and encrypts your identity.\n\n7. You\'ll be presented with the option to save your identity for store keeping in a safe place.</string>
<string name="button_start_create_identity">Azonosító létrehozása</string>
<string name="title_create_identity">SQRL: Azonosító létrehozása</string>
<string name="title_rekey_identity">SQRL - Rekey identity</string>
<string name="rescuecode_show_desc">This page shows your identity rescue code. This code is important that you record somewhere safe. If you need in the future to restore, unlock or remove your accounts this code will be used to verify that you are the correct owner of this identity. Store it <b>safe and off this device</b>. The code is presented left to right starting in the upper left and ending in the lower right. You may add dashes or minuses in your recording to easily distinguish between the groups of 4 characters.</string>
<string name="rescue_code_enter_desc">On this page, we ask you to enter the rescue code that you recorded and saved in a secure place in order to show that you have recorded the correct value.</string>
<string name="button_save_identity_save">Mentés</string>
<string name="txt_identity_name_hint">Azonosító neve (opcionális)</string>
<string name="title_save_identity">SQRL: Azonosító mentése</string>
<string name="button_print_rescue_code">Nyomtatás</string>
<string name="show_identity_image_desc">Az azonosító QR kódja</string>
<string name="url_login_missing_url">Failure! The call to the program had no link attached, please try again.</string>
<string name="main_activity_could_not_create_dir">Nem sikerült átmeneti könyvtárat létrehozni a küldéshez, lehet hogy betelt a tárhelyed?</string>
<string name="rekey_verify_message">Enter rescue code to verify that you have this secure in your possession, and start the process of rekeying the identity.</string>
<string name="button_rekey_verify_next">Következő</string>
<string name="title_rekey_verify">SQRL: Mentő kód ellenőrzése</string>
<string name="title_new_identity_done">SQRL: Azonosító létrehozva</string>
<string name="new_identity_done_message">The identity has been successfully created/rekeyed. In order to use this safely and be able to restore from loss of device we recommend that you export your identity either by scanning QRCode with another device, sending a file to storage or printing the new identity.</string>
<string name="button_new_identity_done_export">Export</string>
<string name="button_new_identity_done">Kész</string>
<string name="camera_permission_request_title">Permission required</string>
<string name="camera_permission_request_desc">In order to create and import identities and also to log in, the app needs to use the camera.\n\nWhen creating an identity, the app uses the camera to gather random data to improve the security of that identity.\n\nIn the case of import and log in, the app gives you the option to scan QR codes in order to input data required for that task. </string>
<string name="introduction_startpage_title">Start</string>
<string name="introduction_nutshell_title">Dióhéjban</string>
<string name="introduction_password_title">Jelszó</string>
<string name="introduction_rescue_code_title">Rescue Code</string>
<string name="introduction_backup_title">Biztonsági mentés</string>
<string name="button_camera_permission_ok">OK</string>
<string name="print_not_available_title">Nyomtatás nem lehetséges</string>
<string name="print_not_available_text">A nyomtatás funkció nem elérhető Android KitKat (4.4) előtti rendszereken</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc1">This printed identity was encrypted with the password it had at the time, and also with its permanent Rescue Code. Since either the correct Password, or the identity\'s Rescue Code, will allow this identity to be used by anyone, neither of those should be stored with, or in any way available with, this printed identity:</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc2">As an additional recovery measure, a textual version of this identity is provided below. If a camera is not available to scan and import the QR code above, the text below may be entered for full identity recovery. However, this is a Rescue Code ONLY version, so this identity\'s Rescue Code will be required for its decryption:</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc3">Please retain and protect this printed version of your identity. With SQRL\'s \"two-party\" operation, no one can compromise your SQRL login security. But this also means that there is no one to turn to if your identity is somehow lost or misplaced. Please treat this identity with the care it deserves. It is your secure and private key to the Internet.</string>
<string name="print_version_string">Page created by Android open-source SQRL client on the</string>
<string name="progress_time_elapsed">Eltelt idő: %s</string>
<string name="progress_time_left">Hátralévő idő: %s</string>
<string name="progress_state_prepare_query">Kérés előkészítése</string>
<string name="progresstate_contact_server">Contacting server</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_identity">Azonosító visszafejtése</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_previous_identity">Előző azonosító visszafejtése</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_rescuecode_identity">Decrypting rescue code identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_identity">Azonosító titkosítása</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_previous_identity">Előző azonosító titkosítása</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_rescue_code_identity">Encrypting rescue code identity</string>
<string name="button_ask_first_button_default">OK</string>
<string name="ask_close">Close question window</string>
<string name="rekey_verify_to_many_rekey_attempts">This identity has been rekeyed so many times that we now need to retire one of the old keys. This means that sites using this, the oldest key, will not recognize this identity.</string>
<string name="export_without_password">Jelszó nélkül</string>
<string name="scan_cancel">Cancelled scan</string>
<string name="scan_incorrect">Hibás QR kód, próbáld újra</string>
<string name="button_forgot_password">Elfelejtetted a jelszavad?</string>
<string name="account_creation_require_full_password">Creating accounts requires more security, please try again and supply full length password.</string>
<string name="button_use_identity">Azonosító használata</string>
<string name="button_advanced_functions">Advanced functions</string>
<string name="import_text_message">Below you can enter the text supplied with your identity to import it. After that\'s done your prompted to enter rescue code and a new password. Each row of the identity text will be verified separately.</string>
<string name="button_text_import">Import with text input</string>
<string name="import_enter_password">Jelszó</string>
<string name="text_input_incorrect">The text entered does not validate to a correct identity string. Checksum error. Please check if the text entered might contain errors.</string>
<string name="text_input_incorrect_on_line">Incorrect input on line:</string>
<string name="title_text_import">SQRL - Text import</string>
<string name="button_text_import_close">Bezárás</string>
<string name="text_input_hint">Input identity rescue text printed on your identity paper version</string>
<string name="error_dialog_title">Hiba történt</string>
<string name="login_identity_quickpass">Jelszó (első %s karakter)</string>
<string name="title_change_password">SQRL: Jelszóváltoztatás</string>
<string name="title_reset_password">SQRL: Jelszóvisszaállítás</string>
<string name="title_disable_account">SQRL: Fiók zárolása</string>
<string name="title_enable_account">SQRL: Fiók zárolás feloldása</string>
<string name="title_remove_account">SQRL: \nFiók eltávolítása</string>
<string name="title_rename_identity">SQRL: Azonosító átnevezése</string>
<string name="title_export_options">SQRL - Export</string>
<string name="title_import">SQRL - Import</string>
<string name="title_account_options">SQRL - Account options</string>
<string name="connection_error">Nem sikerült kapcsolódni a kiszolgálóhoz, próbáld újra</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation">Biztos el akarod távolítani ezt az azonosítót?</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation_positive">Igen</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation_negative">Nem</string>
<string name="title_cps_missing">SQRL - NO Identity Spoof Protection</string>
<string name="cps_missing_text"><b>You should CANCEL, or proceed with caution!</b>\n\nSQRL identity spoof protection has been prevented from operating. This could be the result of a system or web browser configuration setting. But since SQRL anti-spoof system is usually functional, this failure could be the result of an intentional attempt to steal your online identity for the website shown below, by a malicious website that is spoofing its identity.\n\nYou MAY proceed to use SQRL, but you should be VERY SURE that you wish to provide your personal SQRL identity for the website show below to the website you are logging into -- THEY MAY NOT BE THE SAME.</string>
<string name="button_cps_continue">Bejelentkezés mindenképp</string>
<string name="button_cps_cancel">Mégsem</string>
<string name="communication_ip_mismatch"><b>Possible Login Attack Detected</b>\n\nLogin prevented\n\nThe website you were attempting to login to with SQRL may have been \"spoofing\" the actual website\'s identity in an attempt to capture your SQRL identity and use it to login to the real website as you.</string>
<string name="progress_interrupted_title">Progress interrupted</string>
<string name="progress_interrupted_text">You changed orientation or moved around in the application during operation. The current operation might not be completed correctly, please try again.</string>
<string name="action_language">Nyelv</string>
<string name="title_language">Válassz nyelvet</string>
<string name="language_default">Alapértelmezett</string>
<string name="language_arabic">Arab</string>
<string name="language_dutch">Holland</string>
<string name="language_english">Angol</string>
<string name="language_german">Német</string>
<string name="language_hebrew">Héber</string>
<string name="language_french">Francia</string>
<string name="language_japanese">Japán</string>
<string name="language_norwegian">Norvég</string>
<string name="language_swedish">Svéd</string>
<string name="language_spanish">Spanyol</string>
<string name="language_russian">Russian</string>
<string name="language_hungarian">Hungarian</string>
<string name="language_slovenian">Slovenian</string>
<string name="language_czech">Czech</string>
<string name="actionbar_menu">Menu</string>
<string name="error_message_stale_page">The SQRL login page has expired. Please refresh the page, then log in with SQRL.</string>
<string name="error_message_login_failed">SQRL was unable to login to this site. Please refresh the page and try again. If the problem persists please use another login method.</string>
<string name="account_options_alternative_id">Alternative ID</string>
<string name="title_alternative_identity">Alternative identity</string>
<string name="button_alternative_identity">Alternative identity</string>
<string name="startpage_login_with">Login with:</string>
<string name="language_catalan">Catalan</string>
<string name="password_strength_poor">Password strength: poor</string>
<string name="password_strength_medium">Password strength: medium</string>
<string name="password_strength_good">Password strength: good</string>
<string name="password_lowercase">Lowercase</string>
<string name="password_uppercase">Uppercase</string>
<string name="password_symbols">Symbols</string>
<string name="password_digits">Digits</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_lowercase">Indicates whether the password contains lowercase letters</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_uppercase">Indicates whether the password contains uppercase letters</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_digits">Indicates whether the password contains digits</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_symbols">Indicates whether the password contains symbols</string>
<string name="short_password_warning">You are using a very short password. This is highly insecure and should absolutely be avoided!</string>
<string name="rescue_code_incorrect">Incorrect</string>
<string name="invalid_sqrl_file">This file does not appear to be a valid SQRL identity file.</string>
<string name="button_export_share_identity">Share identity</string>
<string name="share_identity_to">Share identity to</string>
<string name="import_identity_file">Import identity file</string>
<string name="title_import_options">SQRL - Import</string>
<string name="install_file_manager_app">Please install a file manager app from the Google Play Store.</string>
<string name="identity_management">Identity management</string>
<string name="title_identity_management">SQRL - Identity Management</string>
<string name="language_chinese">Chinese</string>
<string name="action_password_options">Password options</string>
    <string name="quickpass_not_active">Quickpass was not and is not active</string>
    <string name="quickpass_already_active">QuickPass was already active, and still is</string>
    <string name="quickpass_cancelled">Cancelled QuickPass Initiation</string>
    <string name="quickpass_enable_prompt">Type your SQRL password here to enable QuickPass for `%1$s`.</string>
    <string name="quickpass_enable_message">Enabling QuickPass</string>
    <string name="enable_text">Enable</string>
    <string name="clear_quickpass">Clear QuickPass</string>
    <string name="clear_quickpass_long">Clear QuickPass State Immediately</string>
    <string name="scan_qr_code">Scan QR Code</string>
    <string name="scan_qr_code_long">Scan Web QR Code for Login</string>
    <string name="set_quickpass">Set QuickPass</string>
    <string name="set_quickpass_long">Enter SQRL password to engage QuickPass</string>
    <string name="identity_required">An identity must be created before using this function</string>
    <string name="quickpass_enable_heading">SQRL - Enable QuickPass</string>
</resources>
