<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="app_name">SQRL Login</string>
<string name="introduction_startpage"><b>Secure Quick Reliable Login</b>\n\nWelcome to the help pages. These pages try to explain the different concepts in the protocol in more detail. We will also try to explain the different use cases available to you using this application.\n\nTo use the help pages you can swipe left or right in order to change page.\n\nIf you are interested in looking at the source code of this application, it\'s open source and available at <a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a></string>
<string name="introduction_nutshell"><b>In a Nutshell</b>\n\nBefore you begin using SQRL to log in to websites, your SQRL private identity must be created. You only need one, probably for life, because it reveals NOTHING about you, and it\'s highly secure. It\'s just a very long (77-digit) random number.\n\nFrom then on, whenever you log in with SQRL to a website, your private identity is used to generate another 77-digit number for that one website. Every website you visit sees you as a different number, yet every time you return to the same site, that site\'s unique number is regenerated.\n\nThis allows you to be uniquely and permanently identified, yet completely anonymous.\n\nSince you never need to use an email address or a password, you never give a website your actual identity to protect. If the website\'s SQRL identities are ever stolen, not only would the stolen identities only be valid for that one website, but SQRL\'s cryptography prevents impersonation by using stolen identities.\n\nThis is as good as it sounds. It\'s what we\'ve been waiting for.</string>
<string name="introduction_password"><b>Your SQRL Password</b>\n\nSQRL frees you from the burden of logging into Internet websites by doing it for you. But this means if someone else gained control of your SQRL app, they could impersonate you.\n\nWe solve this problem with an SQRL password which YOU use to login to your SQRL. You decide how much login protection you need. You choose your own password of whatever length and complexity you desire. To impede someone guessing, you set how long any password takes to process. And to make longer, more complex passwords less painful to use, the password\'s first four characters may be used to refresh the full password you recently entered\n\nYou are free to change your password and its various settings at any time. And if you should ever forget or lose your password for any reason, SQRL\'s Rescue Code can be used to recover your access.</string>
<string name="introduction_rescue_code"><b>SQRL\'s Rescue Code</b>\n\nYou and SQRL will probably never need rescuing. But SQRL\'s security is so tight that you MIGHT need a way to unlock things a bit. Here are the two scenarios where you WOULD need rescuing:\n\n• If you changed your password and the new one slipped your mind, there\'s no one to ask. Unlike websites, where you click I forgot my password, your SQRL app doesn\'t know it either. If it did, it could be hacked and used to steal your identity. Backups you have made of your identity will have been saved under the password you were using then, so that might help. But your SQRL-assigned Rescue Code will always forgive any memory lapse.\n• Once you have established your SQRL identity with a website, that identity can ONLY be changed with ITS Rescue Code. If someone WERE to somehow steal your SQRL identity (if your phone was stolen and you used a VERY weak or guessable password, or malware infected your device), they could never replace your identity with theirs. But YOU could retake your stolen identity by creating a new one and using the old identity\'s Rescue Code (which the bad guys would never have) to replace that old identity with your new one.\n\nSQRL\'s Rescue Code is a powerful ally. Write it down, keep it safe and never lose it. You will probably never need it, but if you do you\'ll be very glad you kept it.</string>
<string name="introduction_backup"><b>Why Backup?</b>\n\nYour SQRL private identity is a randomly chosen 77-digit number used to generate each of your individual web identities. NO ONE knows what it is. As you use SQRL to identify yourself to the Internet, your identity BECOMES that 77-digit number. If it is ever lost, so is your Internet identity.\n\nThe other reason to backup your private identity is to copy it to another computer or mobile device. Once your one private SQRL identity has been installed into all of your devices, you can use any of them to easily identify yourself on the Internet.\n\nSQRL provides many simple ways to back up your private identity, and all backups are ALWAYS protected by your SQRL password and Rescue Code.\n\nPrinting backups onto paper, as a small QR code and text (perhaps more than once) is recommended since paper is the original data storage medium. In many ways, it\'s still the best. Simply store it where you store your life\'s other important documents. You can also record your backup to thumb drives, burn them to CD\'s, and store them safely anywhere.\n\nBut PLEASE do make backups, since NO ONE knows your unique 77-digit private identity… not even you!</string>
<string name="welcome_message"><b>Welcome to the Secure Quick Reliable Login (SQRL) client.</b>\n\nThis client app will help you securely and effortlessly log in to websites supporting the SQRL protocol. \n\nIt safely stores and lets you manage your SQRL identity, which the app uses to create unique per-site logins, which are anonymous and give the website owner no secrets to keep.\n\nThere is no connection to any personal information. It just verifies that the same phone that authenticated last time is the same even this time. This makes it possible to create a unique anonymous login on your favorite sites, and you decide how much data you share with the site.\n\nJust to be clear, this application will not hide any identifiers that your phone may provide, but it will not provide any extra data.\n\nYou start the process by creating an identity or scanning an identity generated by another compatible client (like the desktop client supplied by <a href="https://grc.com">https://grc.com</a>) and open it with your password. When your key is loaded you\'re then able to authenticate by scanning QR codes supplied by websites, verifying the address and choosing to log in.\n\nPlease note that permission to use the camera needs to be supplied in order to scan exported secrets, create identities or scan site QR Codes.\n\nTo follow this project on GitHub you can visit\n<a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a></string>
<string name="button_scan_secret">Scan identity QR code</string>
<string name="button_login">Login</string>
<string name="button_intro_close">Close</string>
<string name="action_help">Help</string>
<string name="action_about">About</string>
<string name="about_message_title">About</string>
<string name="about_message_text"><b>Secure Quick Reliable Login</b>\n\nVersion: %s\n\nGithub repository:\n<a href="https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login">https://github.com/kalaspuffar/secure-quick-reliable-login</a>\n\nAuthors:\nDaniel Persson</string>
<string name="decrypt_identity_message">You\'ve successfully scanned your secure identity. Please verify that the rescue data presented below corresponds to the data printed on your key page.</string>
<string name="communication_incorrect_response">Incorrect response, the server didn\'t respond with an error code. Try again later.</string>
<string name="communication_bad_id_association">Bad ID Association: SQRL identity which may be associated with the query nut does not match the SQRL ID used to submit the query.</string>
<string name="communication_client_failure">Client failure: Some information in the query didn\'t make sense to the server so it won\'t handle this request.</string>
<string name="communication_command_failed">Command failed: The web server has encountered a problem successfully processing the query. </string>
<string name="communication_function_not_supported">Function(s) not supported: Requested one or more SQRL functions, that the server does not currently support.</string>
<string name="communication_sqrl_disabled">SQRL authentication for this identity has previously been disabled. To use this identity it needs to be enabled using rescue code.</string>
<string name="communication_transient_error">Transient error: The server indicates that the signature(s) are correct, but something about the query prevented the command from completing.</string>
<string name="title_activity_main">Main</string>
<string name="button_import_identity">Import identity</string>
<string name="button_settings">Settings</string>
<string name="button_create_identity">Create new</string>
<string name="button_remove_identity">Remove</string>
<string name="button_rename_identity">Rename</string>
<string name="button_export_identity">Export</string>
<string name="button_reset_password">Reset password</string>
<string name="button_rekey_identity">Rekey</string>
<string name="button_change_password">Change password</string>
<string name="identity_rename_title">Rename identity</string>
<string name="title_activity_show_identity">Show identity</string>
<string name="button_rename_ok">Rename</string>
<string name="current_identity_title">Current identity</string>
<string name="title_activity_clear_identity">Clear QuickPass</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked_desc">To be secure, QuickPass should be removed after use.\nClick here to clear it from memory.</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked">QuickPass active</string>
<string name="clear_identity_fail">QuickPass is still in memory, unable to be removed</string>
<string name="clear_identity_success">QuickPass removed</string>
<string name="decrypt_identity_fail">Decrypting identity failed, please try with another password.</string>
<string name="encrypt_identity_fail">Encryption of your newly imported identity failed, please try again</string>
<string name="notification_identity_unlocked_title">Your identity is unlocked in your device memory.</string>
<string name="login_verify_domain_text">Using this protocol you may log in to the scanned URL. Please check that the scanned domain is the same as the place you want to visit before entering password.</string>
<string name="login_domain_title">Do you want to login to:</string>
<string name="change_password_retype">Re-type password</string>
<string name="change_password_current">Current password</string>
<string name="change_password_new_password">Create new password</string>
<string name="change_password_retyped_password_do_not_match">Retyped password doesn\'t match new password.</string>
<string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length">QuickPass length (characters)</string>
<string name="settings_password_verify">Password verify (seconds)</string>
<string name="settings_idle_timeout">QuickPass timeout (minutes)</string>
<string name="settings_sqrl_only">Request SQRL only login</string>
<string name="settings_no_sqrl_bypass">Request no SQRL bypass</string>
<string name="settings_save">Save</string>
<string name="settings_cancel">Cancel</string>
<string name="settings_fragment_save">Save</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length_not_number">QuickPass input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_idle_timeout_not_number">QuickPass timeout input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_password_verify_not_number">Password verify input is not a number</string>
<string name="settings_hint_length_to_large">QuickPass value is too large. (0–255)</string>
<string name="save_settings_password">Password</string>
<string name="save_identity_to">Save identity to</string>
<string name="title_activity_advanced">Advanced operations</string>
<string name="main_selected_identity">Selected identity</string>
<string name="identity_reset_password">Reset password</string>
<string name="button_reset_password_ok">Reset</string>
<string name="reset_password_new">New password</string>
<string name="reset_password_desc">In order to set a new password without knowing the old one you need to supply the rescue code given to you at identity creation. Then you supply a new password and we will create a password secured identity.</string>
<string name="save_settings_title">Save settings</string>
<string name="login_title">Login</string>
<string name="import_title">Import identity</string>
<string name="rename_identity_desc">New name</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_1">Part 1</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_2">Part 2</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_3">Part 3</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_4">Part 4</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_5">Part 5</string>
<string name="reset_password_rescuecode_6">Part 6</string>
<string name="change_password_title">Change password</string>
<string name="rescue_code_incorrect_input">Rescue code part need to be 4 numbers</string>
<string name="progress_title">Working</string>
<string name="login_identity_password">Password</string>
<string name="main_identity_removed">Identity removed</string>
<string name="button_lock_account">Disable account</string>
<string name="button_unlock_account">Enable account</string>
<string name="button_remove_account">Remove account</string>
<string name="login_optional_options">Other options</string>
<string name="button_login_options">Options</string>
<string name="disable_account_title">Disable account</string>
<string name="button_disable_account">Disable</string>
<string name="enable_account_title">Enable account</string>
<string name="button_enable_account_enable">Enable</string>
<string name="remove_account_title">Remove account</string>
<string name="button_remove_account_remove">remove</string>
<string name="button_export_show_identity">Show identity</string>
<string name="button_export_save_identity">Save identity</string>
<string name="button_print_identity">Print identity</string>
<string name="title_activity_url_login">Login</string>
<string name="change_password_close">Close change password window</string>
<string name="export_options_close">Close export options window</string>
<string name="login_close">Close login window</string>
<string name="login_optional_close">Close login options window</string>
<string name="remove_account_close">Close remove account window</string>
<string name="rename_close">Close rename window</string>
<string name="reset_password_close">Close reset password window</string>
<string name="save_settings_close">Close save settings window</string>
<string name="title_entropy_gather">Gather entropy</string>
<string name="button_entropy_gather_next">Next</string>
<string name="scan_site_code">Scan QRCode for site</string>
<string name="scan_identity">Scan QRCode for identity</string>
<string name="title_rescuecode_show">Record rescue code</string>
<string name="title_rescuecode_enter">Enter rescue code</string>
<string name="button_rekey_identity_start">Start</string>
<string name="button_create_identity_start">Start</string>
<string name="create_identity_message">Creating a new identity is a process done in 6 steps.\n\n1. First, the camera will be activated and you wave it around to create entropy to make a more secure key.\n\n2. Next up you will be presented with a rescue code that you need to record and keep safe.\n\n3. You will be asked to reenter the rescue code in order to verify that it\'s been recorded correctly.\n\n4. You\'ll select a password for your new identity.\n\n5. The application creates and encrypts your identity.\n\n6. You\'ll be presented with the option to save your identity for store keeping in a safe place.</string>
<string name="rekey_identity_message">Rekeying your identity is a process done in 7 steps.\n\n1. First, you need to enter the old rescue code for this identity in order to verify that you have access to this security code.\n\n2. Second, the camera will be activated and you wave it around to create entropy to make a more secure key.\n\n3. Next up you will be presented with a new rescue code that you need to record and keep safe.\n\n4. You will be asked to reenter the rescue code in order to verify that it\'s been recorded correctly.\n\n5. You\'ll select a password for your new identity.\n\n6. The application creates and encrypts your identity.\n\n7. You\'ll be presented with the option to save your identity for store keeping in a safe place.</string>
<string name="button_start_create_identity">Create identity</string>
<string name="title_create_identity">Create identity</string>
<string name="title_rekey_identity">Rekey identity</string>
<string name="rescuecode_show_desc">This page shows your identity rescue code. This code is important that you record somewhere safe. If you need in the future to restore, unlock or remove your accounts this code will be used to verify that you are the correct owner of this identity. Store it <b>safe and off this device</b>. The code is presented left to right starting in the upper left and ending in the lower right. You may add dashes or minuses in your recording to easily distinguish between the groups of 4 characters.</string>
<string name="rescue_code_enter_desc">On this page, we ask you to enter the rescue code that you recorded and saved in a secure place in order to show that you have recorded the correct value.</string>
<string name="button_save_identity_save">Save</string>
<string name="txt_identity_name_hint">Identity name (Optional)</string>
<string name="title_save_identity">Save identity</string>
<string name="button_print_rescue_code">Print</string>
<string name="show_identity_image_desc">QRCode of identity</string>
<string name="url_login_missing_url">Failure! The call to the program had no link attached, please try again.</string>
<string name="main_activity_could_not_create_dir">Unable to create temporary directory for file to send, do you have too much data on disk?</string>
<string name="rekey_verify_message">Enter rescue code to verify that you have this secure in your possession, and start the process of rekeying the identity.</string>
<string name="button_rekey_verify_next">next</string>
<string name="title_rekey_verify">Verify rescue code</string>
<string name="title_new_identity_done">Identity created</string>
<string name="new_identity_done_message">The identity has been successfully created/rekeyed. In order to use this safely and be able to restore from loss of device we recommend that you export your identity either by scanning QRCode with another device, sending a file to storage or printing the new identity.</string>
<string name="button_new_identity_done_export">Export</string>
<string name="button_new_identity_done">Done</string>
<string name="camera_permission_request_title">Permission required</string>
<string name="camera_permission_request_desc">In order to create and import identities and also to log in, the app needs to use the camera.\n\nWhen creating an identity, the app uses the camera to gather random data to improve the security of that identity.\n\nIn the case of import and log in, the app gives you the option to scan QR codes in order to input data required for that task. </string>
<string name="introduction_startpage_title">Start</string>
<string name="introduction_nutshell_title">Nutshell</string>
<string name="introduction_password_title">Password</string>
<string name="introduction_rescue_code_title">Rescue Code</string>
<string name="introduction_backup_title">Backup</string>
<string name="button_camera_permission_ok">OK</string>
<string name="print_not_available_title">Printing not available</string>
<string name="print_not_available_text">The printing function was not implemented before Android KitKat (4.4)</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc1">This printed identity was encrypted with the password it had at the time, and also with its permanent Rescue Code. Since either the correct Password, or the identity\'s Rescue Code, will allow this identity to be used by anyone, neither of those should be stored with, or in any way available with, this printed identity:</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc2">As an additional recovery measure, a textual version of this identity is provided below. If a camera is not available to scan and import the QR code above, the text below may be entered for full identity recovery. However, this is a Rescue Code ONLY version, so this identity\'s Rescue Code will be required for its decryption:</string>
<string name="print_identity_desc3">Please retain and protect this printed version of your identity. With SQRL\'s \"two-party\" operation, no one can compromise your SQRL login security. But this also means that there is no one to turn to if your identity is somehow lost or misplaced. Please treat this identity with the care it deserves. It is your secure and private key to the Internet.</string>
<string name="print_version_string">Page created by Android open-source SQRL client on the</string>
<string name="progress_time_elapsed">Time elapsed: %s</string>
<string name="progress_time_left">Time left: %s</string>
<string name="progress_state_prepare_query">Preparing query</string>
<string name="progresstate_contact_server">Contacting server</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_identity">Decrypting identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_previous_identity">Decrypting previous identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_descrypting_rescuecode_identity">Decrypting rescue code identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_identity">Encrypting identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_previous_identity">Encrypting previous identity</string>
<string name="progress_state_encrypting_rescue_code_identity">Encrypting rescue code identity</string>
<string name="button_ask_first_button_default">ok</string>
<string name="ask_close">Close question window</string>
<string name="rekey_verify_to_many_rekey_attempts">This identity has been rekeyed so many times that we now need to retire one of the old keys. This means that sites using this, the oldest key, will not recognize this identity.</string>
<string name="export_without_password">Without password</string>
<string name="scan_cancel">Cancelled scan</string>
<string name="scan_incorrect">Incorrect QR code, try again</string>
<string name="button_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
<string name="account_creation_require_full_password">Creating accounts requires more security, please try again and supply full length password.</string>
<string name="button_use_identity">Use identity</string>
<string name="button_advanced_functions">Advanced functions</string>
<string name="import_text_message">Below you can enter the text supplied with your identity to import it. After that\'s done your prompted to enter rescue code and a new password. Each row of the identity text will be verified separately.</string>
<string name="button_text_import">Import with text input</string>
<string name="import_enter_password">Password</string>
<string name="text_input_incorrect">The text entered does not validate to a correct identity string. Checksum error. Please check if the text entered might contain errors.</string>
<string name="text_input_incorrect_on_line">Incorrect input on line:</string>
<string name="title_text_import">Text import</string>
<string name="button_text_import_close">Close</string>
<string name="text_input_hint">Input identity rescue text printed on your identity paper version</string>
<string name="error_dialog_title">An error has occurred</string>
<string name="login_identity_quickpass">Password (First %s characters)</string>
<string name="title_change_password">Change password</string>
<string name="title_reset_password">Reset password</string>
<string name="title_disable_account">Disable account</string>
<string name="title_enable_account">Enable account</string>
<string name="title_remove_account">Remove account</string>
<string name="title_rename_identity">Rename identity</string>
<string name="title_export_options">Export</string>
<string name="title_import">Import</string>
<string name="title_account_options">Account options</string>
<string name="connection_error">Unable to connect to server, please try again</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation">Are you sure you want to remove this identity?</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation_positive">Yes</string>
<string name="remove_identity_confirmation_negative">No</string>
<string name="title_cps_missing">NO Identity Spoof Protection</string>
<string name="cps_missing_text"><b>You should CANCEL, or proceed with caution!</b>\n\nSQRL identity spoof protection has been prevented from operating. This could be the result of a system or web browser configuration setting. But since SQRL anti-spoof system is usually functional, this failure could be the result of an intentional attempt to steal your online identity for the website shown below, by a malicious website that is spoofing its identity.\n\nYou MAY proceed to use SQRL, but you should be VERY SURE that you wish to provide your personal SQRL identity for the website show below to the website you are logging into -- THEY MAY NOT BE THE SAME.</string>
<string name="button_cps_continue">Login anyway</string>
<string name="button_cps_cancel">Cancel</string>
<string name="communication_ip_mismatch"><b>Possible Login Attack Detected</b>\n\nLogin prevented\n\nThe website you were attempting to login to with SQRL may have been \"spoofing\" the actual website\'s identity in an attempt to capture your SQRL identity and use it to login to the real website as you.</string>
<string name="progress_interrupted_title">Progress interrupted</string>
<string name="progress_interrupted_text">You changed orientation or moved around in the application during operation. The current operation might not be completed correctly, please try again.</string>
<string name="action_language">Language</string>
<string name="title_language">Select language</string>
<string name="language_default">Default</string>
<string name="language_arabic">Arabic</string>
<string name="language_dutch">Dutch</string>
<string name="language_english">English</string>
<string name="language_german">German</string>
<string name="language_hebrew">Hebrew</string>
<string name="language_french">French</string>
<string name="language_japanese">Japanese</string>
<string name="language_norwegian">Norwegian</string>
<string name="language_swedish">Swedish</string>
<string name="language_spanish">Spanish</string>
<string name="language_russian">Russian</string>
<string name="language_hungarian">Hungarian</string>
<string name="language_slovenian">Slovenian</string>
<string name="language_czech">Czech</string>
<string name="actionbar_menu">Menu</string>
<string name="error_message_stale_page">The SQRL login page has expired. Please refresh the page, then log in with SQRL.</string>
<string name="error_message_login_failed">SQRL was unable to login to this site. Please refresh the page and try again. If the problem persists please use another login method.</string>
<string name="account_options_alternative_id">Alternate ID</string>
<string name="title_alternative_identity">Alternate identity</string>
<string name="button_alternative_identity">Alternate identity</string>
<string name="startpage_login_with">Login with:</string>
<string name="language_catalan">Catalan</string>
<string name="password_strength_poor">Password strength: poor</string>
<string name="password_strength_medium">Password strength: medium</string>
<string name="password_strength_good">Password strength: good</string>
<string name="password_lowercase">Lowercase</string>
<string name="password_uppercase">Uppercase</string>
<string name="password_symbols">Symbols</string>
<string name="password_digits">Digits</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_lowercase">Indicates whether the password contains lowercase letters</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_uppercase">Indicates whether the password contains uppercase letters</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_digits">Indicates whether the password contains digits</string>
<string name="img_password_contains_symbols">Indicates whether the password contains symbols</string>
<string name="short_password_warning">You are using a very short password. This is highly insecure and should absolutely be avoided!</string>
<string name="rescue_code_incorrect">Incorrect</string>
<string name="invalid_sqrl_file">This file does not appear to be a valid SQRL identity file.</string>
<string name="button_export_share_identity">Share identity</string>
<string name="share_identity_to">Share identity to</string>
<string name="import_identity_file">Import identity file</string>
<string name="title_import_options">Import options</string>
<string name="install_file_manager_app">Please install a file manager app from the Google Play Store.</string>
<string name="identity_management">Identity management</string>
<string name="title_identity_management">Identity Management</string>
<string name="language_chinese">Chinese</string>
<string name="action_password_options">Password options</string>
<string name="quickpass_not_active">Quickpass was not and is not active</string>
<string name="quickpass_already_active">QuickPass was already active, and still is</string>
<string name="quickpass_cancelled">Cancelled QuickPass Initiation</string>
<string name="quickpass_enable_prompt">Type your SQRL password here to enable QuickPass for `%1$s`.</string>
<string name="quickpass_enable_message">Enabling QuickPass</string>
<string name="enable_text">Enable</string>
<string name="clear_quickpass">Clear QuickPass</string>
<string name="clear_quickpass_long">Clear QuickPass State Immediately</string>
<string name="scan_qr_code">Scan QR Code</string>
<string name="scan_qr_code_long">Scan Web QR Code for Login</string>
<string name="set_quickpass">Set QuickPass</string>
<string name="set_quickpass_long">Enter SQRL password to engage QuickPass</string>
<string name="identity_required">An identity must be created before using this function</string>
<string name="idle_timeout_guidance">So you don\'t forget your SQRL master password, the maximum QuickPass timeout is one week ( %1$s minutes), after which you\'ll have to type in the master password again.</string>
<string name="guidance_heading">Guidance</string>
<string name="button_identity_options">Identity options</string>
<string name="identity">Identity</string>
<string name="language_hindi">Hindi</string>
<string name="title_set_password">Set Password</string>
<string name="button_set_password">Set password</string>
<string name="set_password_import_desc">Since the identity being imported has no password set, it is required for you to provide the rescue code given to you at identity creation. You will then chose a new password, which your newly imported identity will be secured with.</string>
<string name="title_activity_identity_settings">Identity Settings</string>
<string name="helptext_password_verify_seconds">Your identity\'s security can be improved by lengthening the time required to verify your full SQRL password. There is NO KNOWN WAY for any attacker, spy agency or government to dramatically speed up this verification process. And since your shorter QuickPass can be used after you have entered your password, you only need to wait once. But someone trying to guess your password needs to wait EVERY TIME they guess.\n\nA five-second verification duration is recommended, but you are free to choose whatever seems best for your convenience and security.</string>
<string name="helptext_quickpass_length">To encourage the use of a longer and more secure access password, SQRL can be configured to only require that your FULL password be provided when it is first used and periodically after that. Once the full password has been entered, for a specified period of time, SQRL may only require the first few characters of your password (called a \"QuickPass\") just to prove it is still you. (How long the \"QuickPass\" is active for is called the \"QuickPass timeout and can also be set in the identity settings). \n\nYou chose between a longer and safer QuickPass or a shorter and more convenient one. What makes this trade-off acceptable is that the QuickPass MUST be entered correctly on the first try or the full password will be required again. \n\nFour characters are the recommended length. But you may set it as low as 1 and as long as your full password.</string>
<string name="helptext_quickpass_timeout">For protection, SQRL\'s QuickPass will be erased after some time. This time span is specified by the QuickPass timeout.\n\nAfter the timeout, SQRL will ask for the FULL password again on the next login.</string>
<string name="helptext_request_sqrl_only_login">Request SQRL-enabled websites to disable all other non-SQRL login methods for maximum security.</string>
<string name="helptext_request_no_sqrl_bypass">Request SQRL-enabled websites to refuse any and all forms of \"I forgot my password\" account recovery.</string>
<string name="language_polish">Polish</string>
<string name="language_finnish">Finnish</string>
<string name="account_missing">No account found on the server</string>
<string name="disable_account_successful">The account is disabled</string>
<string name="enable_account_successful">The account is enabled</string>
<string name="remove_account_successful">The account is removed</string>
<string name="standard_login">Standard login</string>
<string name="helptext_alterate_id">It is usually sufficient and desirable for SQRL to present only one user identity for each website. For this normal operation, alternate identities are not used and the alternate identity name field must remain blank.\n\nBut there may be times when a single SQRL user wishes to present alternate identities to a single website. Such use might be a quick one-time event to appear anonymously as an identity the website has never encountered before and may never encounter again, or a user may choose to make permanent longer-term use of alternate identities.\n\nAlthough these quick alternate identities can be used to create persistent identities, an alternative is to create one or more additional standard SQRL identities. While that approach can be more cumbersome, for some users and uses it may be more appropriate.\n\nAny characters entered into the alternate identity name field will cause a unique and unlinkable alternate identity to be presented to a website. It will be impossible for the website to connect this alternate identity to the normal identity.\n\nIt is appropriate to regard these characters as the alternate identity\'s name because every time the same characters are used the same alternate identity will be presented. Any characters may be used, but since they must be remembered if the same alternate identity will be needed in the future, a meaningful and memorable name should be chosen.\n\nThe alternate identity names are case sensitive, so they must be reused exactly. Any that will be reused may be written down and permanently recorded to eliminate any confusion in the future.\n\nAlso, note that the alternate identity name is not remembered by SQRL and it is not persistent. It will be cleared after use and must be supplied every time the normal identity is to be overridden.</string>
<string name="helptext_disable_account">Despite the use of every possible protection, it is still conceivable that some entity, whether criminal or civil, might somehow obtain access to your SQRL identity. To protect against unauthorized use, any website may be instructed to disable its recognition of your SQRL identity. In this way, SQRL access can be blocked for your most important accounts. In doing this you will be blocking your own access with SQRL, but also the access by anyone who may have somehow obtained your SQRL identity. In other words, you cannot use SQRL to access disabled accounts, but neither can anyone else.\n\nOnly an SQRL client that has been loaded with the identity\'s secret Rescue Code can re-enable SQRL access or replace a compromised SQRL identity with another. And an identity\'s secret Rescue Code can never be stolen or inadvertently disclosed because it is never carried inside the SQRL software and it is never saved onto any storage device.\n\nSince re-enabling a website\'s disabled identity requires the identity\'s Rescue Code, you should be certain that you have access to the Rescue Code before disabling your own access.</string>
<string name="helptext_enable_account">If you have previously disabled your SQRL account for a specific site, you can re-enable it using this function.\n\nPlease note, that this operation will require the use of the identity\'s secret Rescue Code that was given to you upon identity creation.</string>
<string name="helptext_remove_account">There are several reasons why you might wish to completely remove your SQRL identity from a website:\n\nYou might wish to stop using SQRL to authenticate your identity to a particular website. If so, though it is not required, you might wish to permanently remove your SQRL identity.\n\nOr you might be sharing a single SQRL identity with others, but wish to remove one or more websites from access by other users of that SQRL identity.\n\nOr you might wish to hand over SQRL identity authentication for a website to a different SQRL identity. Unless a website supports multiple simultaneous SQRL identities, you would need to first remove your identity so that the replacement identity can then be added.\n\nTo ease the identity transfer process, the removal of your SQRL identity will leave your current web browser session logged into your website account so that another SQRL identity can be immediately added. This might be important if the site only offers SQRL authentication.\n\nTo prevent the possibility of malicious identity replacement, identity removal requires the extra security provided by the identity\'s Rescue Code. If the identity\'s Rescue Code is not already loaded into the SQRL client you will be prompted to provide it before proceeding with the authentication and identity removal.</string>
<string name="cps_auth_aborted_headline">Authentication aborted</string>
<string name="cps_auth_aborted_description">SQRL\'s CPS authentication has been aborted. You will be automatically sent back to the previous page in a few seconds. If this does not work, please press your browser\'s \"BACK\" button or click on the link below.</string>
<string name="cps_auth_aborted_go_back_now">Go back now</string>
<string name="quickpass">QuickPass</string>
<string name="helptext_quickpass_login">Please provide the short \"QuickPass\", which consists of the first few characters of your SQRL identity password.</string>
<string name="helptext_password_login">Please provide the full-length SQRL identity password that you have chosen for this identity.</string>
<string name="title_enable_quickpass">Enable QuickPass</string>
<string name="default_identity_name">My Identity</string>
<string name="language_korean">Korean</string>
<string name="rescue_code_page_headline">This is your Identity\'s Rescue Code</string>
<string name="rescue_code_page_warning">Do not discard this page</string>
<string name="rescue_code_page_description">This is the irreplaceable SQRL Rescue Code for the SQRL identity you are creating.\n\nThis code cannot be recreated and must not be lost, misplaced or destroyed. It will allow you to recover from any disaster that might occur. If your identity\'s password is forgotten, or if your SQRL identity should become compromised, this Rescue Code allows you to recover from any situation. (Some situations may also require your SQRL identity. So be sure to also keep a backup of your identity.)\n\nThis printout should be stored in a safe and secure place where it cannot be found by others, but CAN be retrieved if you should ever need it. That need may never arise. But if it does, you\'ll be glad that you kept it safe and secure.\n\nYour identity\'s Rescue Code is:</string>
<string name="superseded_identity_headline">SQRL Identity replaced</string>
<string name="superseded_identity_text">This SQRL identity has been \"rekeyed\" and replaced and used by some other device to sign-in to this website. When that happened, this website learned of the replacement identity and switched to using it instead of the replaced identity.\n\nAfter rekeying and replacing an identity, it MUST also be replaced on ALL of the other devices where it exists. That has not yet been done for your SQRL identity on this device, so it should be done immediately!\n\nFor your protection, your previous identity, which is still on this device, can no longer be used here. Please transfer your rekeyed identity from the device where it was rekeyed to the SQRL client on this device.\n\nThank you.</string>
</resources>
